Paul Brickwell

Web Developer, Director of IT

Portland Metro Area

907.903.3922

Mello@paulbrickwell.com

https://paulbrickwell.com

I am a professional and detail-oriented Director of IT with over 10 years of experience managing IT systems ranging from on-site servers to entirely cloud-based solutions.

I am pursuing a primary career change into Web Development. In addition to my career experience as a web developer, I have completed JavaScript and Vue.js bootcamps along with extensive and continuous self-taught skills.

Education —

JavaScript Bootcamp Scrimba - 2021

Vue Bootcamp Scrimba - 2021

React Bootcamp Scrimba - Currently Enrolled

BS, Graphic Design Full Sail University 2014 – 2017

Computer Science Classes University of Alaska, Anchorage 2010 – 2014

Experience -

Freelance // 2020 - Current

Web Developer

- Proficient in modern development with **JavaScript** and frameworks like **Vue.js** and **React**.
- Deep understanding of HTML and CSS.
- Strong focus in **organized and readable code** with experiencing managing projects with **Git**.

Craig Taylor Equipment // 2016 - Current

Web Developer // 2017 – Current

- Build various web projects, integrations, and applications such as customer feedback capture portals and post-sale NPS surveys with **Zapier** and **Twilio**.
- Developed and maintain company website built on **Gridsome**, a Jamstack framework for **Vue.js** with **GraphQL** integrations into **Shopify** and our Dealer Management System (DMS).
- Built, designed, and maintain internal employee portal based on **WordPress**.

Director of IT // 2021 – Current

- Manage IT systems for roughly **100 employees at 6 locations** and provide solutions for fully remote employees.
- Maintain firewalls, site-to-site VPNs, subnets, and other network design on **Ubiquiti Edge** and **UniFi** platforms.
- Configure, deploy, and maintain computers and devices on varying operating systems such as Windows 10, MacOS, and iOS.
- Designed, deployed, and maintain support ticketing system with integrations into **Trello**.
- Strategize deployment of IT infrastructure and policies.

System Administrator // 2016 – 2021

- Worked with developers to assist with integration into custom DMS
- Maintained **Windows Server** with **local and cloud Active Directory** policies.
- Created and deployed custom Windows 10 images.
- Provided support to employees for all hardware and software issues.

Experience continued

Marketing Manager // 2017 – 2021

- Identified marketing objectives and designed strategy based on these needs.
- Managed marketing budget including utilizing vendor coop funds.
- Created all print, digital, and radio ads.
- Managed social media accounts and website content.

Brickwell, Inc. // 2015 - 2016

Office Manager

- Maintained scheduling and specialized insurance for large projects.
- Managed bookkeeping and payroll with **QuickBooks**.
- Designed and built online store with **Shopify**.

Immediate Care, Inc. // 2009 - 2015

IT Lead

- Managed multi-city network with VPN connection.
- Managed Windows Servers with **Microsoft Exchange**, custom policies, and roaming profiles.
- Maintained **99.9% uptime** on all services and hardware.

Paul Brickwell

Director of IT, Web Developer

🙇 Portland Metro Area

907.903.3922

https://paulbrickwell.com

Skills -

IT Infrastructure Management
IT Operations
IT Strategy
Network Design

HTML / CSS

JavaScript

Vue.js

React

•••••

••••

•••••